var quiz = [
    {
        question: 'How many soccer players should each team have on the field at the start of each match?',
        options: ['9', '10', '11', '12'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'When Michael Jordan played for the Chicago Bulls, how many NBA Championships did he win?',
        options: ['3', '4', '5', '6'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'What country won the very first FIFA World Cup in 1930?',
        options: ['USA', 'Uruguay', 'Brazil', 'Germany'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'In what year was the first-ever Wimbledon Championship held?',
        options: ['1867', '1877', '1887', '1897'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Which hockey team did Wayne Gretzky play for in the â€˜80s?',
        options: ['Edmonton Oilers', 'Vancouver Canucks', 'Toronto Maple Leafs', 'Calgary Flames'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'The Olympics are held every how many years?',
        options: ['2', '3', '4', '5'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'What do you call it when a player makes three back to back strikes in bowling?',
        options: ['Chicken', 'Kentucky', 'Strike  Out', 'Turkey'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'In American Football, a touchdown is worth how many points?',
        options: ['5', '6', '7', '8'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'What is Canada\'s national sport?',
        options: ['Hockey', 'Baseball', 'Basketball', 'Lacrosse'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the greatest Dallas Maverick in the franchise history?',
        options: ['Dirk Nowitzki', 'Jason Terry', 'Jason Kidd', 'Steve Nash'],
        answer: 0
    }
];